lookuppage.com 2017-12-22

# Look Up Page | Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting [LookUpPage](http://www.lookuppage.com/) (together with all content on the site operated by Cyclicom Holdings Limted or its affiliates ("Cyclicom") (the "Site")).

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the [Terms of Use](http://www.lookuppage.com/lookup-page/terms).

## Introduction

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, pen name, personal profile, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information. Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with the services given under the Site, including but not limited to using the Lookuppage services, you must create an account ("Account") and provide us with your email address, a password that you will use for your Account.

If payment for the Lookuppage Services is made through PayPal account, PayPal`s privacy policy will apply to the information you supply to them. Please note that any user`s Biography, resume, family history, current project or pictures or any other content posted at the direction of user as part of LookupPage services becomes published content and is not considered Personal Information subject to this Privacy Policy.

## The Way We Use Personal Information

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, then we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to make certain offers or services, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site`s services that you are authorized to access.

We may transfer your Personal Information within Cyclicom or to Cyclicom`s third-party service providers, but only to provide services on the Site or to you, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. We may provide Personal Information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

You may choose not to receive email from Cyclicom by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to [privacy@lookuppage.com](mailto:privacy@lookuppage.com). Please note that the email must come from the mail you wish to block.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics, along with other partners, for the purpose of online advertising. Google, as well as other third-party vendors, display our ads on websites across the Internet. To display ads, Google and other third-party vendors use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie). The cookies allow for third-party vendors, including Google, to serve and optimize the ads according to someone’s previous visits to our website. We place the cookie on a browser, and then a 3rd party (Google) reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. These ads may be based on your past visits to our website.. You may opt out of this ad serving by visiting Google’s Ads Preferences Manager. If you are concerned about 3rd party cookies served by networks, you should also visit the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter certain identifying information, should we in the future require such information, to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.

## Notice

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not currently provide your Personal Information to third parties, except for third parties who may perform services on the Site or to you. Nevertheless, we may at a later time choose to make certain offers or services available to our users from third parties. If we do, during the registration process and at certain points thereafter in connection with specific offers, we may ask you whether your Personal Information may be sent to third parties who have products, services and opportunities which may be useful to you. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, your Personal Information (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit to our Site) may be shared with data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. Cyclicom does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Cyclicom`s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your Personal Information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any Personal Information that can identify an individual user.

## Choice

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Cyclicom. The notices we will provide where Cyclicom collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

## Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Cyclicom wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may check your profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information.

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements` effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

## Children`s Privacy

The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.

## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that Cyclicom is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors` rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.

## Commitment

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Cyclicom`s Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@lookuppage.com](mailto:privacy@lookuppage.com). While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

## Your Consent

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Cyclicom`s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of the Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [info@lookuppage.com](mailto:info@lookuppage.com).

Last modified: May 30, 2013

* * *
